russianbare.com 2013-08-26

# Enature.net | Legal | Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Enature.net uses and protects any information that you give Enature.net when you use this website (www.russianbare.com). 

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected while using our website and its features. In any event in which we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified, you can be assured that said information will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement as outlined below.

**Collection of Personal Information**

Within Enature.net, we may seek certain personal information from you, the visitor. Collection of such personal information provided by you, the visitor is solely for the purpose of fulfilling orders and services requested. Provided information is used only by Enature.net and is used to meet said request(s).

Protection of your personally identifiable information is one of our chief concerns. Such personal information submitted to this site is never given or sold to any third party for any reason whatsoever. All transactions that involve your personal information are transmitted via a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) connection, and is always stored on an encrypted environment to ensure the safety of said personal information.

**What we Collect**

Enature.net may, at times require one or more of the following, dependent on the service or services being requested by you, the visitor:

  * Name and address
  * Credit Card details
  * Telephone details
  * E-Mail address

**What we do with collected information**

Enature.net uses visitor's personal information to provide requested services, including, but not limited to:

  * Fulfilling customer orders of requested merchandise
  * Answering e-mails sent to us
  * Answering telephone calls

Order details provided to us, which includes the above mentioned information is stored in our secure database for future reference.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file which is placed on your computer's hard drive. Once accepted, the cookie file is added and the it then helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

The Enature.net website utilizes cookies for the purposes of our shopping cart, member account, and visitor tracking systems. Said cookies are placed on visitor computers as the method in which our system identifies individual users as unique values that work with the aforementioned systems. Said cookie(s) contain only numeric values that are unique to each visitor. Said value is used to reference shopping cart entries, account ID's, and other information in our database.

Users are free to browse our site without enabling cookies, but by doing so will render it impossible to utilize our online store and other important features required to browse our site to its full capacity.

**Note that cookies set by this website are ONLY accessible FROM this website.** Other websites cannot read, and cannot extract any personal information from these cookies.

**Links to Other Websites**

This website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website or its contents. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such external sites, as such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Agreement to Privacy Policy**

By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as set forth above. Enature.net reserves the right to change any of its web site Privacy Policies at any time.
